class QuizData {
  final String question;
  final String optionA;
  final String optionB;
  final String optionC;
  final String optionD;
  final int answer;

  QuizData({
    required this.question,
    required this.optionA,
    required this.optionB,
    required this.optionC,
    required this.optionD,
    required this.answer,
  });
}

List<QuizData> geographyQuiz = [
  QuizData(
      question: "The great Victoria Desert is located in",
      optionA: "Canada",
      optionB: "West Africa",
      optionC: "Australia",
      optionD: "North America",
      answer: 3),
  QuizData(
      question:
          "The Homolographic projection has the correct representation of",
      optionA: "Shape",
      optionB: "Area",
      optionC: "Baring",
      optionD: "Distance",
      answer: 2),
  QuizData(
      question: "The intersecting lines drawn on maps and globes are",
      optionA: "Latitude",
      optionB: "Longitude",
      optionC: "Geographic Grids",
      optionD: "None of the above",
      answer: 3),
  QuizData(
      question: "The light of distant stars is affected by",
      optionA: "The earth's atmosphere",
      optionB: "Interstellar dust",
      optionC: "Both (a) and (b)",
      optionD: "None of the above",
      answer: 3),
  QuizData(
      question:
          "The habitats valuable for commercially harvested species are called",
      optionA: "Coral reefs",
      optionB: "Sea grass bed",
      optionC: "Hot spots",
      optionD: "None of the above",
      answer: 2),
  QuizData(
      question: "The humidity of the air depends upon",
      optionA: "Temperature",
      optionB: "Location",
      optionC: "Weather",
      optionD: "All of the above",
      answer: 4),
  QuizData(
      question: "The iron ore mined at Bailadila is mostly",
      optionA: "Haematite",
      optionB: "Siderite",
      optionC: "Limonite",
      optionD: "Magnetic",
      answer: 1),
  QuizData(
      question: "The temperature increases rapidly after",
      optionA: "Ionosphere",
      optionB: "Exosphere",
      optionC: "Stratosphere",
      optionD: "Troposphere",
      answer: 1),
  QuizData(
      question: "The leading state in producing paper is",
      optionA: "Bihar",
      optionB: "West Bengal",
      optionC: "Kerala",
      optionD: "Orissa",
      answer: 2),
  QuizData(
      question: "The largest dune files are found in",
      optionA: "Middle East",
      optionB: "North Africa",
      optionC: "Both (a) and (b)",
      optionD: "None of the above",
      answer: 3),
];
// List<QuizData> scienceQuiz = [];
// List<QuizData> mathematicsQuiz = [];
// List<QuizData> historyQuiz = [];
// List<QuizData> sportsQuiz = [];
// List<QuizData> artQuiz = [];
// List<QuizData> filmQuiz = [];
// List<QuizData> socialQuiz = [];
// List<QuizData> foodQuiz = [];
// List<QuizData> animalsQuiz = [];
// List<QuizData> birdsQuiz = [];
